[{"id": "article_201", "text": "MIRI, Dec 23  The Democratic Action Party (DAP) must initiate reforms if it seeks to remain relevant in Sarawak, said DAP Socialist Youth (Dapsy) Sarawak chief Peter Hee. In a statement, he said if DAP is committed to go further and remain formidable, the party must be ready to bounce back stronger for the people of Sarawak. He pointed out DAP is now competing with many local-based opposition parties. 'It is different decades or just five years ago when DAP was seen as the only opposition in Sarawak. The results of PRN 12 (12th state election) spoke clearly and we must respond proactively. 'The aspirations of Sarawakians are to take over the GPS (Gabungan Parti Sarawak) government one day and the next step is to see if the new state government can go for more autonomous governance or even independence if circumstances are matured and people are ready; it is a step-by-step progressive political movement,' he claimed. He was clarifying his earlier statement on the need to set up a Sarawak-based youth party. 'I wish to reiterate that it remains my personal and honest opinion taking into account the sentiment and tendency of voting pattern, especially the youth voters in the just concluded PRN-12,' he said. Hee claimed his thoughts sought to provoke brainstorming and much-needed healthy discussion so that DAP Sarawak could reposition in the face of future challenges, with a new political landscape, different scenarios, according to the direction of voters in Sarawak. 'I believe every generation has its own mission and as we grow or move forward, we must be ready to adapt to changing political aspirations of the people. More so when Sarawak has its own dynamic factors, like Sabah's, due to decades long suffering and unfair treatment in the federation. 'There are few possible steps to be initiated in reshaping the party, and my humble expression which was from the bottom of my heart for localising the party is only one of those options, it is not absolute and final,' Hee said. He claimed DAP has other options available and that he has full faith the party's leadership would exercise wisdom for the betterment of the party. 'If my thoughts hurt and offended feelings and were unwelcome by many, I wish to sincerely apologise for my unintentional blunder,' he said. 'If we are from the people, for the people, then by speaking out the voices of the people shall be encouraged.' DAP stood in 26 constituencies in the 12th state election but won just two seats.", "entities": [{"id": 1, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 4}}, {"id": 2, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 18, "end_offset": 41}}, {"id": 3, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 43, "end_offset": 46}}, {"id": 4, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 104, "end_offset": 111}}, {"id": 5, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 118, "end_offset": 137}}, {"id": 6, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 160, "end_offset": 169}}, {"id": 7, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 198, "end_offset": 201}}, {"id": 8, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 318, "end_offset": 325}}, {"id": 9, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 342, "end_offset": 345}}, {"id": 10, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 458, "end_offset": 461}}, {"id": 11, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 497, "end_offset": 504}}, {"id": 12, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 521, "end_offset": 527}}, {"id": 13, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 529, "end_offset": 548}}, {"id": 14, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 617, "end_offset": 628}}, {"id": 15, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 650, "end_offset": 653}}, {"id": 16, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 655, "end_offset": 677}}, {"id": 17, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 994, "end_offset": 1001}}, {"id": 18, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1223, "end_offset": 1226}}, {"id": 19, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1323, "end_offset": 1334}}, {"id": 20, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1479, "end_offset": 1486}}, {"id": 21, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1656, "end_offset": 1663}}, {"id": 22, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1698, "end_offset": 1703}}, {"id": 23, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1996, "end_offset": 1999}}, {"id": 24, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2017, "end_offset": 2020}}, {"id": 25, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2407, "end_offset": 2410}}, {"id": 26, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 2445, "end_offset": 2464}}, {"id": 27, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 146, "end_offset": 153}}, {"id": 28, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 154, "end_offset": 159}}, {"id": 29, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 139, "end_offset": 144}}, {"id": 30, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1205, "end_offset": 1211}}, {"id": 31, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 154, "end_offset": 165}}, {"id": 32, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 146, "end_offset": 165}}, {"id": 33, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 118, "end_offset": 165}}], "relations": [{"id": 250, "head": 13, "tail": 11, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 240, "head": 1, "tail": 4, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 241, "head": 2, "tail": 3, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 242, "head": 5, "tail": 29, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 244, "head": 32, "tail": 5, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 245, "head": 32, "tail": 29, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 246, "head": 31, "tail": 27, "relation": "Physical.Located", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 247, "head": 12, "tail": 13, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 248, "head": 14, "tail": 11, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 249, "head": 15, "tail": 16, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 251, "head": 12, "tail": 11, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 243, "head": 6, "tail": 28, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_202", "text": "KUALA LUMPUR, Jan 19  CIMB Group Bhd is expecting its loans growth in 2022 to exceed the growth in 2021. However, loans growth for Thailand and Indonesia is expected to be below the industry rate in the first half of 2022 (1H22) due to the recalibration of the bank's financing portfolio in the two countries, said AmInvestment Bank in a note today. Nevertheless, it has maintained its 'buy' call on CIMB, with an unchanged fair value of RM6.20 per share based on financial year 2022's (FY22) return on equity (ROE) of 9.8 per cent, noting that foreign shareholdings of the stock rose to 24.7 per cent in December 2021 versus a low of 20.3 per cent in May 2021. Meanwhile, it foresees no significant increase in management overlays from CIMB's loan repayment assistance programme (URUS). It said conservative provisions have already been set aside via top-ups of management overlays in FY20 and FY21, while the group now has better visibility on the risk segments of its loan book. 'We understand that applications for URUS have risen since November 2021, however, the total amount of loans where borrowers have applied for URUS on an absolute value basis has so far been insignificant; below 1.0 per cent of Malaysia's total consumer loans. 'Management alluded to a potential pick-up in applications for URUS towards the end of the deadline (Jan 31, 2022). Nevertheless, we do not anticipate a sharp rise in applications for URUS due to the stricter qualifying criteria on borrowers,' AmInvestment said. RHB Research has also maintained its 'buy' call on CIMB, raising its target price by 14.3 per cent to RM6.30, premised on its expectation that the share price would trend higher on healthy earnings growth in FY22-23 and still decent valuation. 'Although asset quality remains stable, credit cost is expected to stay elevated in the fourth quarter of 2021. 'This is due to further management overlays for URUS, a refresh of macroeconomic factors in the expected credit loss, additional provisions for corporate accounts in Malaysia and Indonesia, and accelerated run-down of its Thai commercial book,' it said in a research note today. Conversely, in a separate note, MIDF Research has downgraded its call on the bank to 'neutral' as it opined that CIMB has a number of headwinds in the short term, most notably a high gross impaired loan ratio, heavy provisions and weak loan growth. Nevertheless, it noted that the bank's long-term prospects remain intact  higher ROE and return on capital employed as result of its kitchen-sinking exercise, a streamlined loan portfolio following its current restructuring, and heavy exposure to the regional market.", "entities": [{"id": 34, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 12}}, {"id": 35, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 22, "end_offset": 36}}, {"id": 36, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 131, "end_offset": 139}}, {"id": 37, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 144, "end_offset": 153}}, {"id": 38, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 315, "end_offset": 332}}, {"id": 39, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 400, "end_offset": 404}}, {"id": 40, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 737, "end_offset": 741}}, {"id": 41, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1209, "end_offset": 1217}}, {"id": 42, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1305, "end_offset": 1309}}, {"id": 43, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1426, "end_offset": 1430}}, {"id": 44, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1486, "end_offset": 1498}}, {"id": 45, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1505, "end_offset": 1517}}, {"id": 46, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1556, "end_offset": 1560}}, {"id": 47, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2027, "end_offset": 2035}}, {"id": 48, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2040, "end_offset": 2049}}, {"id": 49, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 2083, "end_offset": 2087}}, {"id": 50, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2172, "end_offset": 2185}}, {"id": 51, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2253, "end_offset": 2257}}, {"id": 52, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1124, "end_offset": 1128}}, {"id": 53, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 781, "end_offset": 785}}, {"id": 54, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1909, "end_offset": 1913}}], "relations": [{"id": 236, "head": 40, "tail": 53, "relation": "intended public", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 237, "head": 34, "tail": 47, "relation": "capital of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 238, "head": 49, "tail": 36, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 239, "head": 38, "tail": 34, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 234, "head": 35, "tail": 34, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 235, "head": 35, "tail": 39, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1591, "head": 36, "tail": 49, "relation": "country of citizenship", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_203", "text": "KOTA KINABALU: Gabungan Rakyat Sabah (GRS) has been having unofficial meetings on its formalisation, said Sabah Parti Pribumi Bersatu Malaysia (Bersatu) deputy chief Datuk Seri Masidi Manjun. GRS comprises Barisan Nasional, Perikatan Nasional and Parti Bersatu Sabah. It was formed during the 2020 state election. These few days, several Bersatu leaders had called for the coalition to be registered to ensure unity among party component leaders. 'Put it this way, just because there is no announcement (of the progress), it does not mean nothing has been done. 'We have been having informal meetings but it is only proper to be announced when it is done (officially),' he said when met during the 2022 Sabah International Business and Economic Summit here. When asked whether other component party leaders were keen to register the coalition, Masidi said he could not say due to the respective party's stance but said some leaders were eager with the idea. Among those who voiced out about the issue were Bersatu Information chief Khairul Firdaus Akbar and Sabah Armada Chief Fairuz Renddan. Khairul had said that the existing leadership under the GRS government would be able to bring Sabah to the pinnacle of success. He had also added that the never-ending political situation in Peninsular Malaysia should prompt Sabah leaders to chart a direction based on the interests of Sabahans. Fairuz, who is also Pintasan assemblyman, said solidarity among leaders in the GRS is proof they keep their promises and did not underestimate the message given by the people in the last State Election (PRN). 'The people chose us, we move as a coalition chosen by the people of Sabah and for that purpose, it is appropriate for us to continue to move and work to realise what the people expect.'", "entities": [{"id": 55, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 13}}, {"id": 56, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 15, "end_offset": 36}}, {"id": 57, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 38, "end_offset": 41}}, {"id": 58, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 106, "end_offset": 142}}, {"id": 59, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 144, "end_offset": 151}}, {"id": 60, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 153, "end_offset": 165}}, {"id": 61, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 166, "end_offset": 176}}, {"id": 62, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 192, "end_offset": 195}}, {"id": 63, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 206, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 64, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 224, "end_offset": 242}}, {"id": 65, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 247, "end_offset": 266}}, {"id": 66, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 293, "end_offset": 312}}, {"id": 67, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 338, "end_offset": 345}}, {"id": 68, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 698, "end_offset": 751}}, {"id": 69, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 844, "end_offset": 850}}, {"id": 70, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1006, "end_offset": 1025}}, {"id": 71, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1026, "end_offset": 1053}}, {"id": 72, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1058, "end_offset": 1070}}, {"id": 73, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1071, "end_offset": 1091}}, {"id": 74, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1093, "end_offset": 1100}}, {"id": 75, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1149, "end_offset": 1152}}, {"id": 76, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1187, "end_offset": 1192}}, {"id": 77, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1284, "end_offset": 1303}}, {"id": 78, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1318, "end_offset": 1323}}, {"id": 79, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 1379, "end_offset": 1387}}, {"id": 80, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1389, "end_offset": 1395}}, {"id": 81, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1409, "end_offset": 1417}}, {"id": 82, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1418, "end_offset": 1429}}, {"id": 83, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1468, "end_offset": 1471}}, {"id": 84, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1576, "end_offset": 1590}}, {"id": 85, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1592, "end_offset": 1595}}, {"id": 86, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1667, "end_offset": 1672}}, {"id": 87, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 177, "end_offset": 190}}, {"id": 88, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 166, "end_offset": 190}}, {"id": 89, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 153, "end_offset": 190}}, {"id": 90, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 106, "end_offset": 190}}, {"id": 91, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1026, "end_offset": 1031}}, {"id": 92, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1071, "end_offset": 1076}}, {"id": 93, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1058, "end_offset": 1091}}, {"id": 94, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1032, "end_offset": 1053}}, {"id": 95, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1006, "end_offset": 1053}}, {"id": 96, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1077, "end_offset": 1091}}], "relations": [{"id": 208, "head": 56, "tail": 57, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 209, "head": 87, "tail": 61, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 212, "head": 58, "tail": 59, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 214, "head": 68, "tail": 78, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 222, "head": 55, "tail": 76, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 211, "head": 89, "tail": 58, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 213, "head": 89, "tail": 59, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 210, "head": 88, "tail": 60, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 218, "head": 87, "tail": 69, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 219, "head": 65, "tail": 62, "relation": "part of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 220, "head": 64, "tail": 62, "relation": "part of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 221, "head": 63, "tail": 62, "relation": "part of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 227, "head": 94, "tail": 74, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 224, "head": 71, "tail": 70, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 228, "head": 73, "tail": 72, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 229, "head": 96, "tail": 80, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 230, "head": 79, "tail": 78, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 231, "head": 93, "tail": 82, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 232, "head": 84, "tail": 85, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 233, "head": 81, "tail": 78, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 225, "head": 96, "tail": 92, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 223, "head": 94, "tail": 91, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_204", "text": "KOTA KINABALU: Sabah has set up a technical committee to negotiate for a bigger share of revenues from the oil and gas sector in the state. Sabah Chief Minister Datuk Seri Hajiji Noor said the committee chaired by state Local Government and Housing Minister Datuk Seri Masidi Manjun would soon sign the commercial cooperation agreement (CCA) with Petroliam Nasional Bhd (Petronas). 'Through the CCA, Sabah will have greater revenue sharing as well as greater participation and say in our oil and gas matters,' said Hajiji during a briefing on the Malaysia Agreement 1963 (MA63) Special Council for Sabah's lawmakers at the State Legislative Assembly here today. Hajiji said before the briefing, he had discussed the matter with the Petronas president and group chief executive officer Datuk Tengku Muhammad Taufik. The special briefing was to provide insight and convey latest developments to elected representatives about the Sabah and Sarawak governments' demands that have been submitted to the federal government via the MA63 Special Council. The demands include the proposed bill to amend the federal constitution to be in line with the provisions of the MA63, which Sabah and Sarawak had persistently pursued. Hajiji and his Sarawak counterpart Tan Sri Abang Johari Openg had submitted the states' demands at the MA63 Special Council chaired by Prime Minister Datuk Seri Ismail Sabri Yaakob. 'The bill to amend the federal constitution is actually a product of the MA63 Special Council's decision that took into account requests from both Sabah and Sarawak. 'The Sabah government sees the formation of the MA63 Special Council as a crucial phase and a manifestation of the government-of-the-day's readiness to resolve issues that have been agreed before this,' he said. The briefing was also attended by Minister in the Prime Minister's Department (Sabah and Sarawak Affairs) Datuk Seri Dr Maximus Ongkili, Agriculture and Food Industries Minister Datuk Seri Dr Ronald Kiandee and Minister in the Prime Minister's Department (Parliament and Law) Datuk Seri Dr Wan Junaidi Tuanku Jaafar. At the same event, Hajiji witnessed a ceremony in which the federal government submits a letter granting authority to the Sabah government to issue deep sea fishing licences. The letter granting authority was handed over by Kiandee to Sabah Agriculture and Fisheries Minister Datuk Seri Dr Jeffrey Kitingan.", "entities": [{"id": 97, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 13}}, {"id": 98, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 15, "end_offset": 20}}, {"id": 99, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 140, "end_offset": 145}}, {"id": 100, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 146, "end_offset": 160}}, {"id": 101, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 161, "end_offset": 171}}, {"id": 102, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 347, "end_offset": 369}}, {"id": 103, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 371, "end_offset": 379}}, {"id": 104, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 400, "end_offset": 405}}, {"id": 105, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 515, "end_offset": 521}}, {"id": 106, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 598, "end_offset": 603}}, {"id": 107, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 623, "end_offset": 649}}, {"id": 108, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 662, "end_offset": 668}}, {"id": 109, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 732, "end_offset": 740}}, {"id": 110, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 741, "end_offset": 750}}, {"id": 111, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 927, "end_offset": 932}}, {"id": 112, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 937, "end_offset": 944}}, {"id": 113, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1172, "end_offset": 1177}}, {"id": 114, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1182, "end_offset": 1189}}, {"id": 115, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1216, "end_offset": 1222}}, {"id": 116, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1231, "end_offset": 1238}}, {"id": 117, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1319, "end_offset": 1339}}, {"id": 118, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1351, "end_offset": 1365}}, {"id": 119, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1366, "end_offset": 1376}}, {"id": 120, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1377, "end_offset": 1396}}, {"id": 121, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1545, "end_offset": 1550}}, {"id": 122, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1555, "end_offset": 1562}}, {"id": 123, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1569, "end_offset": 1574}}, {"id": 124, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1810, "end_offset": 1853}}, {"id": 125, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1882, "end_offset": 1892}}, {"id": 126, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1893, "end_offset": 1911}}, {"id": 127, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1913, "end_offset": 1944}}, {"id": 128, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1945, "end_offset": 1953}}, {"id": 129, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1954, "end_offset": 1964}}, {"id": 130, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1968, "end_offset": 1982}}, {"id": 131, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1987, "end_offset": 1995}}, {"id": 132, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2052, "end_offset": 2062}}, {"id": 133, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2066, "end_offset": 2091}}, {"id": 134, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2112, "end_offset": 2118}}, {"id": 135, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2153, "end_offset": 2171}}, {"id": 136, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2215, "end_offset": 2220}}, {"id": 137, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2317, "end_offset": 2324}}, {"id": 138, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2369, "end_offset": 2379}}, {"id": 139, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2383, "end_offset": 2399}}, {"id": 140, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 249, "end_offset": 257}}, {"id": 141, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 258, "end_offset": 268}}, {"id": 142, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1251, "end_offset": 1258}}, {"id": 143, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1612, "end_offset": 1632}}, {"id": 144, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1025, "end_offset": 1045}}, {"id": 145, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 172, "end_offset": 183}}, {"id": 146, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 161, "end_offset": 183}}, {"id": 147, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 146, "end_offset": 183}}, {"id": 148, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 220, "end_offset": 248}}, {"id": 149, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 269, "end_offset": 282}}, {"id": 150, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 258, "end_offset": 282}}, {"id": 151, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 249, "end_offset": 282}}, {"id": 152, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 220, "end_offset": 282}}, {"id": 153, "label": "LAW", "position": {"start_offset": 547, "end_offset": 570}}, {"id": 154, "label": "LAW", "position": {"start_offset": 572, "end_offset": 576}}, {"id": 155, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 755, "end_offset": 784}}, {"id": 156, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 791, "end_offset": 813}}, {"id": 157, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 785, "end_offset": 813}}, {"id": 158, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 741, "end_offset": 813}}, {"id": 159, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 732, "end_offset": 813}}, {"id": 160, "label": "LAW", "position": {"start_offset": 1160, "end_offset": 1164}}, {"id": 161, "label": "LAW", "position": {"start_offset": 1025, "end_offset": 1029}}, {"id": 162, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1259, "end_offset": 1277}}, {"id": 163, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1251, "end_offset": 1277}}, {"id": 164, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1366, "end_offset": 1396}}, {"id": 165, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1351, "end_offset": 1396}}, {"id": 166, "label": "LAW", "position": {"start_offset": 1319, "end_offset": 1323}}, {"id": 167, "label": "LAW", "position": {"start_offset": 1471, "end_offset": 1475}}, {"id": 168, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1471, "end_offset": 1491}}, {"id": 169, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1810, "end_offset": 1818}}, {"id": 170, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1826, "end_offset": 1853}}, {"id": 171, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1855, "end_offset": 1880}}, {"id": 172, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1882, "end_offset": 1892}}, {"id": 173, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1882, "end_offset": 1911}}, {"id": 174, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1826, "end_offset": 1911}}, {"id": 175, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1896, "end_offset": 1911}}, {"id": 176, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1965, "end_offset": 1967}}, {"id": 177, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1965, "end_offset": 1982}}, {"id": 178, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1954, "end_offset": 1982}}, {"id": 179, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1945, "end_offset": 1982}}, {"id": 180, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1913, "end_offset": 1982}}, {"id": 181, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2003, "end_offset": 2030}}, {"id": 182, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2032, "end_offset": 2050}}, {"id": 183, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2063, "end_offset": 2065}}, {"id": 184, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2063, "end_offset": 2091}}, {"id": 185, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2052, "end_offset": 2091}}, {"id": 186, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2003, "end_offset": 2091}}, {"id": 187, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2328, "end_offset": 2359}}, {"id": 188, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2360, "end_offset": 2368}}, {"id": 189, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2380, "end_offset": 2382}}, {"id": 190, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2380, "end_offset": 2399}}, {"id": 191, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2369, "end_offset": 2399}}, {"id": 192, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2360, "end_offset": 2399}}, {"id": 193, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2328, "end_offset": 2399}}, {"id": 194, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 547, "end_offset": 593}}, {"id": 195, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1893, "end_offset": 1895}}], "relations": [{"id": 173, "head": 97, "tail": 98, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 174, "head": 145, "tail": 101, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 176, "head": 147, "tail": 99, "relation": "Physical.Located", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 177, "head": 149, "tail": 141, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 178, "head": 102, "tail": 103, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 180, "head": 151, "tail": 148, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 182, "head": 153, "tail": 154, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 183, "head": 162, "tail": 142, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 185, "head": 164, "tail": 118, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 193, "head": 158, "tail": 109, "relation": "chairperson", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 191, "head": 157, "tail": 110, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 190, "head": 157, "tail": 155, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 194, "head": 175, "tail": 195, "relation": "Gen-Aff.Loc-Origin", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 200, "head": 177, "tail": 129, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 202, "head": 179, "tail": 127, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 175, "head": 146, "tail": 100, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 179, "head": 150, "tail": 140, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 181, "head": 145, "tail": 105, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 184, "head": 120, "tail": 119, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 186, "head": 139, "tail": 189, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 189, "head": 192, "tail": 187, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 192, "head": 158, "tail": 109, "relation": "chief executive officer", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 195, "head": 126, "tail": 125, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 196, "head": 173, "tail": 170, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 197, "head": 170, "tail": 171, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 198, "head": 174, "tail": 169, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 199, "head": 130, "tail": 176, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 201, "head": 178, "tail": 128, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 203, "head": 133, "tail": 183, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 205, "head": 185, "tail": 181, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 206, "head": 186, "tail": 131, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 188, "head": 191, "tail": 188, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 207, "head": 184, "tail": 132, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 187, "head": 190, "tail": 138, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_205", "text": "KUALA LUMPUR: Foreign investors continue to enter Malaysia's equity market for the third week at a faster pace from the week prior, MIDF Research said. Based on data from Bursa Malaysia, foreign investors bought RM116.45 million net of local equities last week, compared to RM11.35 million net in the preceding week. MIDF Research said as market reopened on Monday last week, foreign investors and retailers bought RM60.14 million and RM5.89 million net of local equities respectively. Local institutions started the week as net sellers with RM66.03 million, it added. MIDF Research said the largest net buying by the foreign investors was recorded on Tuesday at RM89.04 million. 'The momentum of foreign net inflow on Wednesday slowed down to RM21.52 million following the Federal Reserve's decision to increase interest rate,' it said. Only net outflow from foreign funds came in on Friday where it amounted to -RM99.07 million. 'This was despite upbeat Malaysia's economic data which sustained double-digit exports growth in December-21,' it said. MIDF Research said January had so far seen a foreign net inflow of RM0.46 billion. Meanwhile, the firm said retailers were net sellers for majority of the week except on Monday and Thursday. The largest net selling by the retailers was recorded on Tuesday at RM26.37 million. For the week, retailers net sold RM30.69 million worth of equities in Bursa. MIDF Research said local institutions recorded cumulative weekly net selling to the tune of RM85.74 million. Local institutions were net sellers for all days of the week except on Friday (RM110.44 million), with the largest net selling on Monday at RM66.03 million. In terms of participation the retail investors, MIDF Research said local institutions and the foreign investors recorded a weekly movement of -11.07 per cent, -20.59 per cent and -16.20 per cent respectively in average daily trade value.", "entities": [{"id": 196, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 12}}, {"id": 197, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 50, "end_offset": 58}}, {"id": 198, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 132, "end_offset": 145}}, {"id": 199, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 171, "end_offset": 185}}, {"id": 200, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 317, "end_offset": 330}}, {"id": 201, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 569, "end_offset": 582}}, {"id": 202, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 774, "end_offset": 789}}, {"id": 203, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 956, "end_offset": 964}}, {"id": 204, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1051, "end_offset": 1064}}, {"id": 205, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1397, "end_offset": 1402}}, {"id": 206, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1404, "end_offset": 1417}}, {"id": 207, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1718, "end_offset": 1731}}], "relations": [{"id": 172, "head": 196, "tail": 197, "relation": "capital of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_206", "text": "Cambodia are easy meat for Malaysia in their AFF Cup opener on Dec 6 at Singapore's Bishan Stadium?   Not as easy as Malaysian fans would think, according to national coach Tan Cheng Hoe.    He has analysed the Southeast Asian minnows, and concluded that they will offer strong resistance to Harimau Malaya in Group B.   Cheng Hoe was impressed with the Angkor Warriors who defeated Guam 3-1 on aggregate in an Asian Cup qualifier last month.   'Cambodia are playing well under coach Ryu Hirose with the guidance of team manager Keisuke Honda. They are improving fast as a team, so it will not be so easy for us,' said Cheng Hoe.    The experience of Japanese Honda, who featured in three World Cups (2010, 2014 and 2018), has helped Cambodia make inroads in the game.    'I do not want our players to be overconfident in the opening AFF Cup match.  'They have to focus on playing to instructions.     'They have several top players who ply their trade abroad. Chan Vathanaka, who had played in the M-League, is still in the game, and he is good.   'We have to be careful against Cambodia. They are hardworking and do a lot of running during matches, and they do not give up easily,' said Cheng Hoe.   After Cambodia, Harimau Malaya will take on Laos on Dec 9, followed by Vietnam (Dec 12) and Indonesia (Dec 19).   On Tuesday, 11 players reported for national training at Wisma FAM. The others will come in later due to the ongoing Malaysia Cup competition.   Cheng Hoe will only get his full squad of 28 players on Dec 1, a day after the Malaysia Cup final.", "entities": [{"id": 208, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 45, "end_offset": 52}}, {"id": 209, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 72, "end_offset": 81}}, {"id": 210, "label": "FACILITY", "position": {"start_offset": 84, "end_offset": 98}}, {"id": 211, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 117, "end_offset": 126}}, {"id": 212, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 173, "end_offset": 186}}, {"id": 213, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 211, "end_offset": 226}}, {"id": 214, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 292, "end_offset": 306}}, {"id": 215, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 8}}, {"id": 216, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 27, "end_offset": 35}}, {"id": 217, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 321, "end_offset": 330}}, {"id": 218, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 354, "end_offset": 369}}, {"id": 219, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 411, "end_offset": 420}}, {"id": 220, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 478, "end_offset": 483}}, {"id": 221, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 484, "end_offset": 494}}, {"id": 222, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 529, "end_offset": 542}}, {"id": 223, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 619, "end_offset": 628}}, {"id": 224, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 689, "end_offset": 699}}, {"id": 225, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 834, "end_offset": 841}}, {"id": 226, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 961, "end_offset": 975}}, {"id": 227, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 999, "end_offset": 1007}}, {"id": 228, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1189, "end_offset": 1198}}, {"id": 229, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1218, "end_offset": 1232}}, {"id": 230, "label": "FACILITY", "position": {"start_offset": 1373, "end_offset": 1382}}, {"id": 231, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1433, "end_offset": 1457}}, {"id": 232, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1461, "end_offset": 1470}}, {"id": 233, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1540, "end_offset": 1552}}, {"id": 234, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 734, "end_offset": 742}}, {"id": 235, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1080, "end_offset": 1088}}, {"id": 236, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1208, "end_offset": 1216}}, {"id": 237, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1246, "end_offset": 1250}}, {"id": 238, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1273, "end_offset": 1280}}, {"id": 239, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1294, "end_offset": 1303}}, {"id": 240, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 158, "end_offset": 172}}, {"id": 241, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 446, "end_offset": 454}}, {"id": 242, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 660, "end_offset": 665}}, {"id": 243, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 383, "end_offset": 387}}, {"id": 244, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 516, "end_offset": 528}}, {"id": 245, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 651, "end_offset": 659}}, {"id": 246, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 158, "end_offset": 186}}, {"id": 247, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 478, "end_offset": 494}}, {"id": 248, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 516, "end_offset": 542}}], "relations": [{"id": 281, "head": 210, "tail": 209, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 282, "head": 212, "tail": 240, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 283, "head": 212, "tail": 217, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 284, "head": 221, "tail": 220, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 285, "head": 222, "tail": 244, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 287, "head": 246, "tail": 214, "relation": "Org-Aff.Sports-Affiliation", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 288, "head": 246, "tail": 214, "relation": "coach of sports team", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 289, "head": 208, "tail": 210, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 291, "head": 247, "tail": 241, "relation": "coach of sports team", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 292, "head": 247, "tail": 241, "relation": "Org-Aff.Sports-Affiliation", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 293, "head": 248, "tail": 241, "relation": "Org-Aff.Sports-Affiliation", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 294, "head": 248, "tail": 245, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}]}, {"id": "article_207", "text": "AARHUS: Almost two decades of heartbreak finally ended on Sunday for Indonesia as they captured the Thomas Cup, overcoming defending champions China 3-0 in the final at the Ceres Arena. This was Indonesia's 20th appearance in a Thomas Cup final and a record-extending 14th crown.  They achieved their last win in 2002 in Guanzhou when they defeated Malaysia 3-2. World No 5 Anthony Sinisuka Ginting survived a tense opening match to outlast world No 27 Lu Guang Zu 18-21, 21-14, 21-16 in 77 minutes to give Indonesia the lead. Guang Zu had replaced top-ranked Shi Yu Qi, who suffered an injury in the semi-finals against Japan on Saturday. 'Today's match against Guang Zu was the toughest in three meetings. However, I knew he would be pressing hard for a win, but I was calm throughout the match,' Anthony told Bernama on Sunday. Seventh-ranked Fajar Alfian-Muhammad Rian Ardianto showed their class in the next match, beating He Ji Ting-Zhou Hao Dong 21-12, 21-19 to double Indonesia's lead in front of 2,000 spectators. Indonesia clinched their winning point when World No 7 Jonatan Christie defeated 65th-ranked Li Shifeng 21-14, 18-21, 21-14.  'Winning the Thomas Cup is my biggest achievement, bigger than my Asian Games gold medal,' Jonatan told the Badminton World Federation.  Although veteran Hendra Setiawan did not play in the final, it was a meaningful outing for the Indonesian captain, who had never won the Thomas Cup throughout his illustrious career. However, the celebration on stage was a subdued affair for Indonesia as there was no hoisting of their red and white flag despite the national anthem being played. It is because of a sanctioned by the World Anti-Doping Agency for being non-compliant with the anti-doping code.  The Indonesian Badminton Association (PBSI) flag was instead raised during the victory ceremony", "entities": [{"id": 249, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 6}}, {"id": 250, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 69, "end_offset": 78}}, {"id": 251, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 100, "end_offset": 110}}, {"id": 252, "label": "FACILITY", "position": {"start_offset": 173, "end_offset": 184}}, {"id": 253, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 228, "end_offset": 238}}, {"id": 254, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 321, "end_offset": 329}}, {"id": 255, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 374, "end_offset": 398}}, {"id": 256, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 453, "end_offset": 464}}, {"id": 257, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 527, "end_offset": 535}}, {"id": 258, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 560, "end_offset": 569}}, {"id": 259, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 663, "end_offset": 671}}, {"id": 260, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 799, "end_offset": 806}}, {"id": 261, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 812, "end_offset": 819}}, {"id": 262, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 976, "end_offset": 985}}, {"id": 263, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1078, "end_offset": 1094}}, {"id": 264, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1116, "end_offset": 1126}}, {"id": 265, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1162, "end_offset": 1172}}, {"id": 266, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1215, "end_offset": 1226}}, {"id": 267, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1240, "end_offset": 1247}}, {"id": 268, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1257, "end_offset": 1283}}, {"id": 269, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1303, "end_offset": 1318}}, {"id": 270, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 1381, "end_offset": 1391}}, {"id": 271, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1392, "end_offset": 1399}}, {"id": 272, "label": "WORK_OF_ART", "position": {"start_offset": 1423, "end_offset": 1433}}, {"id": 273, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1670, "end_offset": 1694}}, {"id": 274, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1751, "end_offset": 1783}}, {"id": 275, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1785, "end_offset": 1789}}, {"id": 276, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 143, "end_offset": 148}}, {"id": 277, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 195, "end_offset": 204}}, {"id": 278, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 349, "end_offset": 357}}, {"id": 279, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 507, "end_offset": 516}}, {"id": 280, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 621, "end_offset": 626}}, {"id": 281, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1023, "end_offset": 1032}}, {"id": 282, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1528, "end_offset": 1537}}, {"id": 283, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 846, "end_offset": 858}}, {"id": 284, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 859, "end_offset": 881}}, {"id": 285, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 928, "end_offset": 938}}, {"id": 286, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 939, "end_offset": 952}}], "relations": [{"id": 170, "head": 274, "tail": 275, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 171, "head": 263, "tail": 267, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 273, "head": 252, "tail": 249, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 275, "head": 277, "tail": 253, "relation": "winner", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 276, "head": 251, "tail": 252, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 277, "head": 269, "tail": 271, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 278, "head": 269, "tail": 270, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 279, "head": 270, "tail": 250, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 280, "head": 256, "tail": 257, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1593, "head": 263, "tail": 265, "relation": "winner", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1594, "head": 263, "tail": 266, "relation": "winner", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1595, "head": 263, "tail": 262, "relation": "country for sport", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1592, "head": 250, "tail": 270, "relation": "country of citizenship", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1596, "head": 255, "tail": 262, "relation": "country for sport", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1597, "head": 283, "tail": 262, "relation": "country for sport", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 1598, "head": 284, "tail": 262, "relation": "country for sport", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_208", "text": "KUALA LUMPUR: Malaysia needs new policies to reset the country's economy and protect the well-being of the people, especially vulnerable households and businesses. Sunway Group founder and chairman Tan Sri Dr Jeffrey Cheah said the country's economy, which had been badly affected by Covid-19, needed extraordinary initiatives especially in 2022 Budget. Cheah said the policies needed to be very different from the old, taking into consideration the suffering of the rakyat. 'We need policies that will encourage business and also bring back confidence in the government institution. The government needs to get people to really come out united as one to bring prosperity into the country's economic system,' he said at the virtual Merdeka and Malaysia Day edition of MIDF Conversations today. Cheah said the government also needed to relook at its Malaysia My Second Home (MM2H) policy, considering an improvement to the programme as a strategy to assist in the country's recovery. 'To me, (changes to the) MM2H now is very demotivating. Instead of giving incentives, they are adding more hurdles to the foreigners. These people have brought in billions of ringgit to the country as they bring in tourists. 'We can easily capture a lot of cash on this tourism with these people bringing their families and friends to visit Malaysia. Why does the government want to change this policy? 'Luckily, now the minister said they will relook at it. I hope that the government will put their full commitment on this matter, but if they don't, it is going to be wasted,' he said. On August 11, the government said the MM2H would be reactivated with nine new conditions after the programme was suspended in August last year in view of the global Covid-19 pandemic. The new conditions, among others, require participants to be in the country for at least 90 cumulative days in a year and have an offshore income of at least RM40,000 a month compared to RM10,000 previously. They must also have a fixed deposit account of at least RM1 million, with 50 per cent maximum withdrawal allowed for the purpose of buying property or spending on health and children's education. Previously, there was no minimum stay requirement for participants who only needed to place RM300,000 in fixed deposits while for those over 50, the amount was RM150,000. Also new are processing fees of between RM5,000 and RM2,500, which was not imposed previously. On Wednesday, Home Minister Datuk Seri Hamzah Zainudin said the government was prepared to re-examine the new criteria imposed on the programme.", "entities": [{"id": 287, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 12}}, {"id": 288, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 14, "end_offset": 22}}, {"id": 289, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 164, "end_offset": 176}}, {"id": 290, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 198, "end_offset": 205}}, {"id": 291, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 209, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 292, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 354, "end_offset": 359}}, {"id": 293, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 744, "end_offset": 756}}, {"id": 294, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 768, "end_offset": 786}}, {"id": 295, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 794, "end_offset": 799}}, {"id": 296, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1324, "end_offset": 1332}}, {"id": 297, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2439, "end_offset": 2452}}, {"id": 298, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2453, "end_offset": 2463}}, {"id": 299, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 177, "end_offset": 184}}, {"id": 300, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 189, "end_offset": 197}}, {"id": 301, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 206, "end_offset": 208}}, {"id": 302, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 206, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 303, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 198, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 304, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 177, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 305, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 164, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 306, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 732, "end_offset": 739}}, {"id": 307, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2464, "end_offset": 2479}}, {"id": 308, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2453, "end_offset": 2479}}, {"id": 309, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2439, "end_offset": 2479}}], "relations": [{"id": 159, "head": 287, "tail": 288, "relation": "capital of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 160, "head": 291, "tail": 301, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 164, "head": 304, "tail": 289, "relation": "Org-Aff.Founder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 162, "head": 303, "tail": 300, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 165, "head": 304, "tail": 289, "relation": "chairperson", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 166, "head": 304, "tail": 289, "relation": "founded by", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 168, "head": 308, "tail": 297, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 167, "head": 307, "tail": 298, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 161, "head": 302, "tail": 290, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 163, "head": 303, "tail": 299, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_209", "text": "GEORGE TOWN, Dec 1  The Penang government does not plan to form any alliance with the opposition parties in the state, the state legislative assembly heard today. Penang Chief Minister Chow Kon Yeow said the state government is now stable and fully supported by Penang voters so there was no need for such an alliance. He said the state has implemented several agendas under the Confidence and Supply Agreement (CSA) signed by Pakatan Harapan (PH) leaders at the federal level. 'One of it is the amendment to the state constitution in 2012 to prevent an elected assemblyman from hopping parties,' he said. Other than this, he said the state legislative assembly has also approved the 2018 amendment to the state constitution to limit an individual from holding the chief minister's post to only two terms. 'The Penang state government, under PH, often leads the way in bringing changes to ensure the people's rights are defended at all time,' he said. Chow was reading his reply to an oral question by Dr Afif Bahardin (Bersatu-Seberang Jaya) on whether the state will offer an agreement similar to the CSA to the opposition for the sake of Penang people. Meanwhile, Dr Afif also asked Chow if the state is ready to provide the same amount of allocations to the opposition assemblymen as the ones allocated for PH assemblymen. Chow replied that the opposition assemblymen in Penang are receiving allocations of between RM300,000 and RM400,000 from the federal government. 'So we believe that the opposition assemblymen have received adequate funding from the federal government,' he said. He added that PH assemblymen in the state were not afforded the same treatment from the federal government as they did not receive any allocation from the federal government.", "entities": [{"id": 310, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 11}}, {"id": 311, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 24, "end_offset": 41}}, {"id": 312, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 123, "end_offset": 149}}, {"id": 313, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 163, "end_offset": 184}}, {"id": 314, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 262, "end_offset": 268}}, {"id": 315, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 427, "end_offset": 442}}, {"id": 316, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 444, "end_offset": 446}}, {"id": 317, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 635, "end_offset": 661}}, {"id": 318, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 765, "end_offset": 779}}, {"id": 319, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 811, "end_offset": 834}}, {"id": 320, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 842, "end_offset": 844}}, {"id": 321, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 952, "end_offset": 956}}, {"id": 322, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1167, "end_offset": 1174}}, {"id": 323, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1186, "end_offset": 1190}}, {"id": 324, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1311, "end_offset": 1313}}, {"id": 325, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1327, "end_offset": 1331}}, {"id": 326, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1375, "end_offset": 1381}}, {"id": 327, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1452, "end_offset": 1470}}, {"id": 328, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1603, "end_offset": 1605}}, {"id": 329, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 185, "end_offset": 198}}, {"id": 330, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 163, "end_offset": 198}}, {"id": 331, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 1141, "end_offset": 1147}}, {"id": 332, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1167, "end_offset": 1169}}, {"id": 333, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1314, "end_offset": 1325}}, {"id": 334, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1273, "end_offset": 1284}}, {"id": 335, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1606, "end_offset": 1617}}, {"id": 336, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1002, "end_offset": 1004}}, {"id": 337, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1002, "end_offset": 1018}}, {"id": 338, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1020, "end_offset": 1041}}, {"id": 339, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1005, "end_offset": 1018}}], "relations": [{"id": 154, "head": 310, "tail": 314, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 155, "head": 315, "tail": 316, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 158, "head": 330, "tail": 311, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 153, "head": 329, "tail": 313, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 156, "head": 339, "tail": 336, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 157, "head": 339, "tail": 322, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_210", "text": "KUALA LUMPUR, Feb 9  Bursa Malaysia closed at its intraday high today with the benchmark composite index rising 1.4 per cent on continuous buying support in selected financial services stocks led by Maybank and Public Bank, a dealer said. The two heavyweights contributed a combined 6.26 points to the gains in the market bellwether. At 5pm, the FTSE Bursa Malaysia KLCI (FBM KLCI) surged 21.42 points to 1,551.51 from 1,530.09 at yesterday's close. The index, which opened 1.10 points higher at its intraday low of 1,531.19, moved steadily throughout the session. Overall market breadth was positive with advancers outnumbering decliners 579 to 412, while 411 counters were unchanged, 811 untraded, and 10 others suspended. Total turnover improved to 2.96 billion units worth RM2.52 billion against 2.85 billion units worth RM2.17 billion at yesterday's close. Rakuten Trade Sdn Bhd vice-president of equity research Thong Pak Leng said the key regional markets also showed upbeat performance following positive cues from Wall Street overnight. 'Investors continued their bargain-hunting activities while at the same time optimistic on positive corporate earnings news across the region. 'As for the local bourse, we expect the uptrend to continue due to improved market sentiment and renewed optimism,' he told Bernama. Thong said the FBM KLCI was expected to trade within the 1,545-1,560 range for the remainder of the week. Regionally, Singapore's Straits Times Index rose 0.45 per cent to 3,417.11, Japan's Nikkei 225 increased 1.08 per cent to 27,579.87, Hong Kong's Hang Seng Index added 2.06 per cent to 24,829.99, while China's SSE Composite Index put on 0.79 per cent to 3,479.95. Back home, heavyweights, Maybank advanced 15 sen to RM8.50, Public Bank added nine sen to RM4.30, both CIMB and Digi improved 16 sen to RM5.40 and RM3.99, respectively, and Press Metal firmed 19 sen to RM6.49. Of the actives, VSolar rose half-a-sen to 1.5 sen, AirAsia added 2.5 sen to 68.5 sen, DneX perked up 4.5 sen to RM1.02, while MMAG eased half-a-sen to eight sen and Sedania soared 10.5 sen to 50.5 sen. On the index board, the FBM ACE rose 60.10 points to 6,307.71, FBM 70 expended 92.19 points to 13,704.99, FBM Emas Index climbed 128.65 points to 11,158.08, FBMT 100 Index jumped 132.43 points to 10,838.78, and the FBM Emas Shariah Index bagged 101.78 points to 11,848.31. Sector-wise, the Financial Services Index surged 284.95 points to 16,112.73, the Plantation Index added 65.14 points to 6,683.72, and the Industrial Products and Services Index was 2.19 points better at 207.84. The Main Market volume narrowed to 1.75 billion shares valued at RM2.23 billion against 2.02 billion shares valued at RM1.95 billion on Tuesday. Warrants turnover improved to 305.24 million units worth RM38.68 million from 267.55 million units worth RM32.84 million previously. The ACE Market volume advanced to 903.64 million shares valued at RM248.37 million versus 560.48 million shares valued at RM189.10 million yesterday. Consumer products and services counters accounted for 356.16 million shares traded on the Main Market, industrial products and services (452.38 million), construction (66.64 million), technology (306.87 million), SPAC (nil), financial services (94.43 million), property (90.34 million), plantation (21.96 million), REITs (6.94 million), closed/fund (2,000), energy (132.40 million), healthcare (90.18 million), telecommunications and media (24.97 million), transportation and logistics (61.75 million), and utilities (42.35 million)", "entities": [{"id": 340, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 12}}, {"id": 341, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 21, "end_offset": 35}}, {"id": 342, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 199, "end_offset": 206}}, {"id": 343, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 211, "end_offset": 222}}, {"id": 344, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 918, "end_offset": 932}}, {"id": 345, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1313, "end_offset": 1320}}, {"id": 346, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1322, "end_offset": 1327}}, {"id": 347, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1440, "end_offset": 1449}}, {"id": 348, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1452, "end_offset": 1471}}, {"id": 349, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1504, "end_offset": 1509}}, {"id": 350, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1512, "end_offset": 1522}}, {"id": 351, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1561, "end_offset": 1570}}, {"id": 352, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1573, "end_offset": 1588}}, {"id": 353, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1629, "end_offset": 1634}}, {"id": 354, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1716, "end_offset": 1723}}, {"id": 355, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1751, "end_offset": 1762}}, {"id": 356, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1794, "end_offset": 1798}}, {"id": 357, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1803, "end_offset": 1807}}, {"id": 358, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1864, "end_offset": 1875}}, {"id": 359, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1952, "end_offset": 1959}}, {"id": 360, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1987, "end_offset": 1991}}, {"id": 361, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2066, "end_offset": 2073}}, {"id": 362, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 884, "end_offset": 917}}, {"id": 363, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 862, "end_offset": 883}}, {"id": 364, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 884, "end_offset": 932}}, {"id": 365, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 862, "end_offset": 932}}, {"id": 366, "label": "PRODUCT", "position": {"start_offset": 1637, "end_offset": 1656}}, {"id": 367, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1917, "end_offset": 1923}}, {"id": 368, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2027, "end_offset": 2031}}], "relations": [{"id": 149, "head": 342, "tail": 340, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 150, "head": 343, "tail": 340, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 151, "head": 364, "tail": 363, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 152, "head": 344, "tail": 362, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_211", "text": "PUTRAJAYA: The National Recovery Council (NRC) has proposed for the full reopening of the country's borders as early as March 1, without the need for mandatory quarantine.  However, its chairman Tan Sri Muhyiddin Yassin said travellers must undergo the Covid-19 test before their departure and upon arrival in Malaysia, as per the recommendation of the Health Ministry.  'The reopening of international borders needs to be implemented in a planned manner and based on current risk assessments,' he told a press conference after chairing the NRC meeting today.  Muhyiddin said the reopening of borders would support the country's economic recovery process and other industries related to tourism.  'By doing so, the country's recovery process will be accelerated, where the investors can come, international tourists can visit and subsequently revive our tourism and aviation industries.'  Asked if the reopening is only for selected countries, Muhyiddin replied: 'The reopening is for all countries.'  This, Muhyiddin said as Health Minister Khairy Jamaluddin, who was also present, told the meeting that the Omicron Covid-19 variant is now present in many countries.  'As such, we cannot be selective by allowing only selected countries.'    He said should the government agree with the suggestion by the council, further preemptive Covid-19 measures, specific conditions and the standard operating procedures (SOP) such as pre-departure Covid-19 PCR test and others will be announced by the Health Ministry.  Muhyiddin said based on the briefing earlier by the Health Ministry he was confident that the country's public health system can manage daily positive Covid-19 cases based on past experiences.  On Nov 11, Muhyiddin told a press conference that Malaysia's borders should be opened to international visitors by Jan 1 this year.  The reopening, however, had been pushed back indefinitely following the spike in infections involving the Omicron variant.  Malaysian borders have remained largely closed since March 2020, when the first national lockdown was imposed.  Certain exemptions, however, have been made for students, Malaysians returning home from abroad, permanent residents and businessmen.  Meanwhile, when asked about the upcoming Johor State Election, Muhyiddin said as Parti Pribumi Bersatu Malaysia (Bersatu) president he was hoping that some relaxation on the SOP will be given during the campaigning period.  'I hope there is a flexibility given to allow the democratic system to run more transparently and those who are involved, from any party, are allowed to campaign, with some expected limitations.'", "entities": [{"id": 369, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 9}}, {"id": 370, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 15, "end_offset": 40}}, {"id": 371, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 42, "end_offset": 45}}, {"id": 372, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 186, "end_offset": 219}}, {"id": 373, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 310, "end_offset": 318}}, {"id": 374, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 353, "end_offset": 368}}, {"id": 375, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 561, "end_offset": 570}}, {"id": 376, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 944, "end_offset": 953}}, {"id": 377, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1008, "end_offset": 1017}}, {"id": 378, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1042, "end_offset": 1059}}, {"id": 379, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1493, "end_offset": 1508}}, {"id": 380, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1511, "end_offset": 1520}}, {"id": 381, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1563, "end_offset": 1578}}, {"id": 382, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1716, "end_offset": 1725}}, {"id": 383, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1755, "end_offset": 1763}}, {"id": 384, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 1962, "end_offset": 1971}}, {"id": 385, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 2132, "end_offset": 2142}}, {"id": 386, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 2250, "end_offset": 2270}}, {"id": 387, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2272, "end_offset": 2281}}, {"id": 388, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2290, "end_offset": 2320}}, {"id": 389, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2322, "end_offset": 2329}}, {"id": 390, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 2331, "end_offset": 2340}}, {"id": 391, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 186, "end_offset": 194}}, {"id": 392, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 195, "end_offset": 202}}, {"id": 393, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 203, "end_offset": 219}}, {"id": 394, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 195, "end_offset": 219}}, {"id": 395, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 541, "end_offset": 552}}, {"id": 396, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1026, "end_offset": 1041}}, {"id": 397, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1026, "end_offset": 1059}}], "relations": [{"id": 133, "head": 370, "tail": 371, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 134, "head": 393, "tail": 392, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 135, "head": 394, "tail": 391, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 136, "head": 372, "tail": 370, "relation": "chairperson", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 145, "head": 387, "tail": 388, "relation": "chairperson", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 146, "head": 387, "tail": 389, "relation": "chairperson", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 148, "head": 384, "tail": 383, "relation": "country of citizenship", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 137, "head": 372, "tail": 371, "relation": "chairperson", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 138, "head": 369, "tail": 373, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 139, "head": 393, "tail": 375, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 140, "head": 378, "tail": 396, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 141, "head": 397, "tail": 379, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 142, "head": 384, "tail": 383, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 143, "head": 388, "tail": 389, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 144, "head": 387, "tail": 390, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_212", "text": "BERA: Prices of essential goods are expected to stabilise and recover by early next year. This is when most countries reopen their borders, allowing economic activities to slowly return to normal, said Prime Minister Datuk Seri Ismail Sabri Yaakob. He explained that the current price increase came about because borders at several countries were closed due to the Covid-19 pandemic and the subsequent movement control order. This prevented Malaysia from importing the essential items needed. Ismail Sabri adds a surge in demand but a drop in supply will also result in prices increasing. He said although the price increase was beyond the control of the government, it nevertheless, did not remain idle, nor did it claim that its hands were tied on the matter.  He added that the government has introduced various measures to alleviate the burden faced by the people following the hike in essential goods prices. 'The government will always look into ways to help the people by prioritising their interests as we do not want them to endure hardship or suffer. Ismail Sabri said the ongoing Keluarga Malaysia (Malaysian Family) sales programme is among the measures taken by the government to assist the people.   'Since vegetable farmers are experiencing an increase in pesticide price, the government has provided subsidies and incentives hoping that the vegetable prices will drop. 'The Keluarga Malaysia sales programme offers discounts up to 50 per cent and will be carried out for three months till March next year until the prices of goods stabilise,' he said. Ismail Sabri said this in his speech when opening the Bera parliamentary-level mass circumcision programme at the Bera District Council Hall here today.  A total of 350 children aged between five and 12 years old took part in the mass circumcision ceremony which was sponsored by Ismail Sabri's constituency office. On a separate matter, Ismail Sabri said the Rural Development Ministry has been given an additional RM500 million to intensify developments in rural areas nationwide. 'This is to ensure those living in rural areas will be provided with proper infrastructures including roads and housing projects', he said.", "entities": [{"id": 398, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 4}}, {"id": 399, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 202, "end_offset": 216}}, {"id": 400, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 217, "end_offset": 227}}, {"id": 401, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 441, "end_offset": 449}}, {"id": 402, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 493, "end_offset": 505}}, {"id": 403, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1061, "end_offset": 1073}}, {"id": 404, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1568, "end_offset": 1580}}, {"id": 405, "label": "FACILITY", "position": {"start_offset": 1682, "end_offset": 1708}}, {"id": 406, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1848, "end_offset": 1860}}, {"id": 407, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1906, "end_offset": 1918}}, {"id": 408, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1928, "end_offset": 1954}}, {"id": 409, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 217, "end_offset": 247}}, {"id": 410, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 202, "end_offset": 247}}, {"id": 411, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 228, "end_offset": 247}}, {"id": 412, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 374, "end_offset": 382}}], "relations": [{"id": 126, "head": 409, "tail": 399, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 125, "head": 411, "tail": 400, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 128, "head": 411, "tail": 402, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 130, "head": 410, "tail": 401, "relation": "head of government", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 131, "head": 405, "tail": 398, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 132, "head": 412, "tail": 401, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_213", "text": "National No 1 men's doubles  Aaron Chia-Soh Wooi Yik have run into  a new bogey pair in Japan's Takuro Hoki-Yugo Kobayashi. The world No 8 just can't seem to get the better of Hoki-Kobayashi as the Malaysians suffered their second straight defeat to the World No 16 during yesterday's Group D tie of the Thomas Cup. The Olympic bronze medallists came into the match looking for revenge following their straight games defeat to Hoki-Kobayashi in the semi-finals of the Sudirman Cup earlier this month. Instead, it was Hoki-Kobayashi who made a mockery of the rankings and Olympic achievements as they powered to a 21-13, 21-13 win yesterday. It proved to be a crucial win as the 2019 World Championships runners-up gave Japan a much needed 2-0 lead after world No 1 Kento Momota had downed world No 8 Lee Zii Jia in the opening men's singles match. And Aaron-Wooi Yik believe it is now on them to find a solution to get out of this rut. 'I think their style of play favoured the outcome, especially since we've played them so many times,' said Aaron. 'It is the outcome we would have liked, but now we need to figure out how to manage it in future matches.' Wooi Yik added: 'I think Hoki-Kobayashi came into the match with more self-confidence after beating us at the Sudirman Cup. 'They used a similar strategy, and we definitely need to improve the next time we face them. 'I think what we really need is to work out a strategy to counter opponents who have analysed our game and found our weaknesses. 'There is not much time as we play again tomorrow, but we will come back to give it our best.'", "entities": [{"id": 413, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 88, "end_offset": 93}}, {"id": 414, "label": "NORP", "position": {"start_offset": 198, "end_offset": 208}}, {"id": 415, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 304, "end_offset": 314}}, {"id": 416, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 468, "end_offset": 480}}, {"id": 417, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 571, "end_offset": 578}}, {"id": 418, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 678, "end_offset": 702}}, {"id": 419, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 765, "end_offset": 777}}, {"id": 420, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 800, "end_offset": 811}}, {"id": 421, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1043, "end_offset": 1048}}, {"id": 422, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1157, "end_offset": 1165}}, {"id": 423, "label": "EVENT", "position": {"start_offset": 1267, "end_offset": 1279}}, {"id": 424, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 719, "end_offset": 724}}, {"id": 425, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 29, "end_offset": 39}}, {"id": 426, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 40, "end_offset": 52}}, {"id": 427, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 96, "end_offset": 107}}, {"id": 428, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 108, "end_offset": 122}}, {"id": 429, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 176, "end_offset": 180}}, {"id": 430, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 181, "end_offset": 190}}, {"id": 431, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 427, "end_offset": 431}}, {"id": 432, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 432, "end_offset": 441}}, {"id": 433, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 517, "end_offset": 521}}, {"id": 434, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 522, "end_offset": 531}}, {"id": 435, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 852, "end_offset": 857}}, {"id": 436, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 858, "end_offset": 866}}, {"id": 437, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1182, "end_offset": 1186}}, {"id": 438, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1187, "end_offset": 1196}}], "relations": [{"id": 110, "head": 425, "tail": 414, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 111, "head": 426, "tail": 414, "relation": "Gen-Aff.CRRE", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 112, "head": 431, "tail": 416, "relation": "winner", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 113, "head": 432, "tail": 416, "relation": "winner", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 114, "head": 425, "tail": 415, "relation": "participant", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 115, "head": 426, "tail": 415, "relation": "participant", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 116, "head": 427, "tail": 415, "relation": "participant", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 117, "head": 428, "tail": 415, "relation": "participant", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 118, "head": 425, "tail": 435, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 119, "head": 426, "tail": 436, "relation": "given name", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 120, "head": 425, "tail": 416, "relation": "participant", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 121, "head": 426, "tail": 416, "relation": "participant", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 122, "head": 427, "tail": 413, "relation": "country for sport", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 123, "head": 428, "tail": 413, "relation": "country for sport", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_214", "text": "KUALA LUMPUR: Mah Sing Group Bhd proposes the government introduce additional initiatives in the upcoming Budget 2022 that will help accelerate the recovery of the property industry in Malaysia. Founder and group managing director Tan Sri Leong Hoy Kum said the government should offer more measures targeting first-time homebuyers, specifically in-home financing, to boost homeownership. 'This includes reinstating maximum loan tenure to 40 years and setting the higher margin of financing up to 100 per cent for first property to help the M40 and B40 groups who are affected during the pandemic,' Leong said in a statement. The company also hopes the government can consider implementing the developer interest bearing scheme (DIBS) for first-time home buyers. He said this would allow buyers to have the option to not service their loan interest and rentals at the same time during the construction period. 'Additionally, we proposed the government to grant the extension of Home Ownership Campaign (HOC) for another year, as the campaign has been proven to be vital in helping home buyers to secure their home while reducing the housing overhang situation since it was launched,' he said. Meanwhile, Leong said the government should consider terminating the real property gains tax (RPGT) on properties sold after five years as an impetus to boost the secondary market. He said the re-imposition of RPGT on properties sold five years after the duration would possibly dampen the secondary residential property segment recovery and discourage long-term investment. 'This will also indirectly improve the home buyers' sentiment in property purchase,' he said. Besides, Leong also proposes that the government reduce the minimum threshold for foreign property ownership to RM600,000, although the current minimum threshold for foreign property ownership varies according to state. 'We hope the government can review and standardise the minimum threshold to RM600,000 across all states, especially in the areas with high property overhang such as the Klang Valley, Johor and Penang. 'With the current currency rate, it will attract foreigners to invest in tangible investments, which will help reduce the property overhang,' he said. On the Malaysia My Second Home Programme's (MM2H) programme, Leong has made several proposals to the government, such as lowering the qualifying minimum income, liquid assets, and fixed deposits instead of a drastic increase currently. Other recommendations are to impose different classes of applications, tailor the program for various foreign applicants, all existing MM2H pass holders should not be affected by the new rules, and the duration of the MM2H pass shall remain at 10 years. Other items on the wish list are reducing the compliance cost to lower house prices to benefit home buyers and introducing incentives for developments incorporating green features. The 2022 Budget is expected to be tabled in Parliament on October 29, 2021.", "entities": [{"id": 439, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 12}}, {"id": 440, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 14, "end_offset": 32}}, {"id": 441, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 185, "end_offset": 193}}, {"id": 442, "label": "TITLE", "position": {"start_offset": 231, "end_offset": 238}}, {"id": 443, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 239, "end_offset": 252}}, {"id": 444, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 599, "end_offset": 604}}, {"id": 445, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1204, "end_offset": 1209}}, {"id": 446, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1671, "end_offset": 1676}}, {"id": 447, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2051, "end_offset": 2063}}, {"id": 448, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2065, "end_offset": 2070}}, {"id": 449, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2075, "end_offset": 2081}}, {"id": 450, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 2295, "end_offset": 2300}}, {"id": 451, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2949, "end_offset": 2959}}, {"id": 452, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 195, "end_offset": 202}}, {"id": 453, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 207, "end_offset": 230}}, {"id": 454, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 231, "end_offset": 252}}, {"id": 455, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 195, "end_offset": 252}}], "relations": [{"id": 101, "head": 440, "tail": 439, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 102, "head": 439, "tail": 441, "relation": "capital of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 103, "head": 443, "tail": 442, "relation": "award received", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 104, "head": 455, "tail": 440, "relation": "Org-Aff.Founder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 105, "head": 455, "tail": 440, "relation": "director / manager", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 106, "head": 455, "tail": 440, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 107, "head": 454, "tail": 453, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 108, "head": 448, "tail": 441, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 109, "head": 449, "tail": 441, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}]}, {"id": "article_215", "text": "KUALA LUMPUR, Sept 1  Carsome Group, an integrated car e-commerce platform, has announced the completion of its US$170 million (RM705 million) Series D2 round of funding, bringing the company's valuation to US$1.3 billion, thus cementing its position as Malaysia's largest tech unicorn. In a statement today, Carsome said the funding round is complemented by new credit facilities of US$30 million, bringing the total funds raised to US$200 million. The Series D2 round  the largest equity investment in Carsome's history  saw participation from one of the largest sovereign wealth funds in the region, as well as a pool of new international investors such as Catcha Group, MediaTek and Penjana Kapital. It also saw strong participation from existing shareholders including Asia Partners, Gobi Partners, 500 Southeast Asia, Ondine Capital, MUFG Innovation Partners, Daiwa PI Partners and others. Rothschild & Co acted as the financial advisor to Carsome for the deal. According to Carsome co-founder and group chief executive officer Eric Cheng, the latest funding round enables the company to accelerate its organic growth in the retail and auto-financing business. 'We are deeply honoured and encouraged by the confidence and support accorded by our investors. 'We are geared up to achieve even greater heights while rolling out Southeast Asia's integrated car e-commerce platform, now further solidified by various strengths within the ecosystem,' added Cheng. Carsome's latest funding round will empower its strategic focus on the growth and expansion of its business-to-consumer (B2C) business. This year alone, Carsome has opened at least seven B2C retail centers known as Carsome Experience Centres across Malaysia, Indonesia and Thailand, with several more in the pipeline for the rest of the year. The company has also opened its first vehicle reconditioning centre in Malaysia to add to its array of retail services and boost consumer confidence in its Carsome Certified cars. The funding injection also strengthens Carsome's offering in auto-financing for car buyers and used car dealers. In addition to its numerous financing products, Carsome had recently launched auto financing facilities for graduates who typically face challenges in obtaining loan approvals from conventional banks. Apart from championing the growth of its B2C business, Carsome's Series D2 funding is also expected to boost its capabilities in strategic investments and mergers and acquisitions. This year, the company has acquired an all-equity stake in PT Universal Collection, a Jakarta-based car and motorcycle auction service. It had also entered into a strategic partnership with leading listings and content automotive platform, iCar Asia, to build the largest automotive ecosystem in Southeast Asia, with more transactions expected over the next six months. Carsome transacts more than 100,000 cars on an annualised basis, which translates to around US$1 billion in revenue.", "entities": [{"id": 456, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 0, "end_offset": 12}}, {"id": 457, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 22, "end_offset": 35}}, {"id": 458, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 254, "end_offset": 262}}, {"id": 459, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 309, "end_offset": 316}}, {"id": 460, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 504, "end_offset": 511}}, {"id": 461, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 660, "end_offset": 672}}, {"id": 462, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 674, "end_offset": 682}}, {"id": 463, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 687, "end_offset": 702}}, {"id": 464, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 774, "end_offset": 787}}, {"id": 465, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 789, "end_offset": 802}}, {"id": 466, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 804, "end_offset": 822}}, {"id": 467, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 824, "end_offset": 838}}, {"id": 468, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 840, "end_offset": 864}}, {"id": 469, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 866, "end_offset": 883}}, {"id": 470, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 896, "end_offset": 911}}, {"id": 471, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 946, "end_offset": 953}}, {"id": 472, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 981, "end_offset": 988}}, {"id": 473, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1034, "end_offset": 1044}}, {"id": 474, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1331, "end_offset": 1345}}, {"id": 475, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 1457, "end_offset": 1462}}, {"id": 476, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1464, "end_offset": 1471}}, {"id": 477, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1617, "end_offset": 1624}}, {"id": 478, "label": "FACILITY", "position": {"start_offset": 1679, "end_offset": 1705}}, {"id": 479, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1713, "end_offset": 1721}}, {"id": 480, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1723, "end_offset": 1732}}, {"id": 481, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1737, "end_offset": 1745}}, {"id": 482, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 1878, "end_offset": 1886}}, {"id": 483, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2026, "end_offset": 2033}}, {"id": 484, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2148, "end_offset": 2155}}, {"id": 485, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2356, "end_offset": 2363}}, {"id": 486, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2541, "end_offset": 2564}}, {"id": 487, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2568, "end_offset": 2581}}, {"id": 488, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2722, "end_offset": 2731}}, {"id": 489, "label": "LOCATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2778, "end_offset": 2792}}, {"id": 490, "label": "ORGANIZATION", "position": {"start_offset": 2852, "end_offset": 2859}}, {"id": 491, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 989, "end_offset": 999}}, {"id": 492, "label": "ROLE", "position": {"start_offset": 1004, "end_offset": 1033}}, {"id": 493, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 989, "end_offset": 1044}}, {"id": 494, "label": "PERSON", "position": {"start_offset": 981, "end_offset": 1044}}], "relations": [{"id": 75, "head": 457, "tail": 458, "relation": "country of origin", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 76, "head": 456, "tail": 458, "relation": "capital of", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 77, "head": 457, "tail": 459, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 78, "head": 473, "tail": 492, "relation": "occupation", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 80, "head": 493, "tail": 472, "relation": "founded by", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 81, "head": 493, "tail": 472, "relation": "Org-Aff.Founder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 82, "head": 493, "tail": 472, "relation": "chief executive officer", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 83, "head": 493, "tail": 472, "relation": "Org-Aff.Employment", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 84, "head": 478, "tail": 479, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 86, "head": 478, "tail": 481, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 85, "head": 478, "tail": 480, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 87, "head": 479, "tail": 474, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 88, "head": 480, "tail": 474, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 89, "head": 481, "tail": 474, "relation": "Part-Whole.Geo", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 90, "head": 485, "tail": 488, "relation": "partnership with", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 91, "head": 460, "tail": 461, "relation": "investor", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 93, "head": 460, "tail": 463, "relation": "investor", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 92, "head": 460, "tail": 462, "relation": "investor", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 94, "head": 460, "tail": 464, "relation": "Org-Aff.Shareholder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 99, "head": 460, "tail": 469, "relation": "Org-Aff.Shareholder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 98, "head": 460, "tail": 468, "relation": "Org-Aff.Shareholder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 97, "head": 460, "tail": 467, "relation": "Org-Aff.Shareholder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 96, "head": 460, "tail": 466, "relation": "Org-Aff.Shareholder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 95, "head": 460, "tail": 465, "relation": "Org-Aff.Shareholder", "relation_source": "ACE05"}, {"id": 100, "head": 470, "tail": 471, "relation": "NO_RELATION", "relation_source": "DocRED"}, {"id": 272, "head": 486, "tail": 487, "relation": "location", "relation_source": "DocRED"}]}, {"id": "article_216", "text": "GEORGE TOWN: The state Health Department is conducting an internal probe on a Monday incident where a woman had to deliver her newborn in a car as she could not arrive at the hospital on time. State Health Department director Dr Ma'arof Sudin said the investigation would be conducted immediately to improve the delivery of health and medical services to the people. 'The department would like to refer to the viral statement on social media regarding a baby being born inside a car after the mother received initial treatment at the Seberang Jaya Hospital (HSJ) on Dec 27. 'For the information, the HSJ confirmed that the mother had sought treatment at the hospital and examination found that she had signs of early birth. She was then allowed to go home upon the doctor's advice,' he said today Dr Ma'arof said the department held a meeting with the woman's next-of-kin today to get more information and decided to conduct an internal investigation. Meanwhile, Dr Ma'arof urged the public or patients who had any questions, complaints or suggestions to contact the hospital directly so that investigations or improvements could be implemented immediately. Social media was abuzz with news of a woman who delivered her baby inside the car as she could not arrive at the hospital on time. The woman had initially gone to a government hospital because she was already showing signs of delivering the baby. She, however, claimed that she was asked to go home first because it was still not time for her to give birth. The woman then appealed to the hospital to allow her to be admitted to the ward as she is staying in Sungai Ara, Bayan Lepas which is quite far from the hospital, but her appeal was ignored. Shortly after arriving home, the woman told her husband she had to be rushed to the hospital again at about 7pm due to 'bleeding'. However, the travelling time to two government hospital